KARTHIK KUMAR

WEB DEVELOPER

CONTACT

+91 9959860275,+91 9160180220

karthikkumarambati@gmail.com

https://karthikkumarambati.github.io/kar thik_kumar/

Punjagutta, Hyderabad 500082

TECHNICAL SKILLS

HTML5

CSS

Java script

BootStrap

Wordpress

PHP

MySql

Angular Js

Core Java

OJS Software

Web Development

LANGUAGES

English

Telugu

Hindi

INTREST

Adventures Bike Ridings Cooking Singing Songs Learning

SOCIAL LINK

https://www.linkedin.com/in/karthikkumar-ambati-716a6a224

PROFILE

I'm a Creative web developer and UI/UX Designer from Hyderabad, India, working in web development. I have one year experienced on front end development on technology based and past seven months i started working on a tool based like wordpress and OjS, also full stack development on PHP.I will be enjoying turning complex problems into simple, beautiful, and intuitive designs. My job is to build a website, which is functional and user-friendly at the same time attractive.

Moreover, I will be adding a personal touch to the product and making sure that is eye-catching and easy to use.I aim to bring across your message and identity in the most creative way.

WORK EXPERIENCE AND INTERNSHIPS

Web Developer

SunRise Enterprises

Nov 2022 - Aug 2023

- Managed the Development and Maintenance of client side applications
- Developed user interface with modern Java script frame works, HTML5 and CSS3, Which improves user satisfaction.
- created and oversaw wireframe designs from client requests.
- Created a mobile responsive user Experience with CSS Flexbox that allowed cross-platform accessibility to the website

Web Developer

INTERNSHALA

(Dec 2021 - Mar 2022)

• Internshala is one of the best platforms to learn new technologies and new programming with good mentors. this is the platform which choose to learn when I'm in beginner. the organization which I choose completed my training with an internship.

Web Developer

Skill Vertex

2021-2022

Project: https://github.com/karthikkumarambati/skill_vertex-major-project-

Technologies:

Html5 CSS javascript PHP

MySQL

Description:

This is one of our major projects which I did with our teammates during a training period. the project is about short clip movie uploading and data storing into databases also retrieving into website

KARTHIK KUMAR

WEB DEVELOPER

SKILLS

- Programming
- Debugging
- · Problem Solving
- · Critical Thinking
- Collaboration
- Communication

EDUCATION

Bachelors degree

Telangana University, Kamaready

BSC(MSCs) 2018-2021

CGPA: 7.5

Intermidiate

SR junior college, Nizamabad

Mpc 2016-2018 CGPA: 8.0

PERSONAL DETAILS

Name : Ambati Karthik kumar

S/O : A.Srinivas
Date of birth : 10-Feb-1998
Martual status : Single
Nationality : Indian
Religion : Hindu

Permanent Address: Gottimukala,

Makloor, Nizamabad Telangana, 503246.

portfolio

https://karthikkumarambati.github.io/karthik_kumar/

Web Developer

Yaaron Media

Project:

https://skpropertiesb4u.com/home-land.html

Technologies:

Html5 CSS

Java script

Description:

SK properties which is one of my real-time project frameworks in yaaron media. the project is about a real estate framework in which an admin and agent can upload properties that are also visible to users on the website.

PERSONAL PROJECT'S

coffee bar

Project:

https://karthikkumarambati.github.io/coffee_world/

Technologies:

Html5 CSS Java script

Description:

The project is about a coffee menu bar, which can make an order from the list of the menu site online

sk properties (Backend)

Project:

http://karthik12.lovestoblog.com/

Technologies:

Html5 CSS Java script PHP MySql Bootstrap

Description:

The project is about real estate, in which one can add his/her property for sale or rent online

SK properties which is one of my projects. the project is about a real estate framework in which an admin and agent can upload properties that are also visible to users on the website.

CERTIFICATES

SKILL VERTEX

A certificate in full-stack web development in skillvertex on "July 2022".

Internshala

A certificate in full-stack web development in Internshala on "Mar 2022".

KARTHIK KUMAR

WEB DEVELOPER

I am writing to apply for your job application role in your company. I am a hard-working and determined professional seeking an opportunity to succeed in a dynamic company such as yours.

I have completed my BSC in MSCs from Government Arts & Science College. My keen interest in Web Programming has enabled me to develop a good knowledge of software development. That enhanced my technical capacity and performance. However, I can assure you that I am a quick learner and adaptive to any technology.

I firmly believe that I can make a positive contribution to your company and I have enclosed my resume to provide more information on my skills and experience. I would welcome the opportunity to meet you for an in-depth discussion and I will make myself available at your first convenience.

SINCERELY,

KARTHIK KUMAR